American Chicle Company Records
American Chicle Company Records
- General files
  - American Chicle Company
    - Patents
      - Canada
        - Coho-Chewing Gum Base (Box 17)
        - H.V. Dunham, 2 folders (Box 17)
        - Leon W. Geller (Box 17)
        - General (Box 17)
        - Maintenance of Freshness of Chewing Gum (Box 17)
        - Meyer Sen Sen Tin Box (Box 17)
        - Peter Paul, Inc. (Box 17)
        - Phenolphthalein in Chewing Gum (Box 17)
        - Arthur Russell (Box 17)
        - Schandein and Lynn Folding Display Boxes (Box 17)
        - Schandein and Lynn (Box 17)
        - Stranders Display Rack, 2 folders (Box 17)
        - E.R. Stucky Glass Display Jar, 2 folders (Box 17)
        - Tempters Step Display Box (Box 17)
        - Tempters Transparent Box (Box 17)
      - Legal Protection of Novel Packages (Box 17)
      - Mexico
        - Tempters Crystal Box (Box 17)
      - U.S.
        - Air Wick Type Compound and Fluid Employing Chlorophyll (Box 17)
        - Anti-Oxidizing Agents for Rubber (Box 17)
        - Wm. C. Arkell and Marion G. Mastin (Box 17)
        - Auguste H. Aubin (Box 17)
        - G.R. Baker, 2 folders (Box 17)
        - Richard K. Baker (Box 17)
        - Barbieri-Process of Making Sheets (Box 17)
        - Cesare Barbieri, 2 folders (Box 17)
        - Bartlett Tin Box (Box 17)
        - Bartlett Tin Box, Dispensing Cover for Containers (Box 17)
        - T. Bayer, Means for and Method of Forming Gum (Box 17)
        - W.A. Beatty
          - Copies of Various Patents (Box 17)
          - Jelutong Product and Method of Making It (Box 17)
          - Moisture Proof Packages, 5 folders (Box 17)
          - Treatment of Rubber (Box 17)
        - P.L. Becker, Paraffin Dipped Package (Box 17)
        - Beech-Nut Packing Company, Chewing Gum Base (Box 17)
        - Beeman's Pepsin Coin Mats (Box 17)
        - W.L. Belvin, Chewing Gum Base (Box 17)
        - A. Biddle, Composition of Gum Chicle Dispersed in an Aqueous Celloid (Box 17)
        - Arthur Biddle, Composition of Gum Chicle (Box 17)
        - Bilotti, Medicinal Coating, 2 folders (Box 17)
        - Bilotti/Hainer, Mechanism of Release, Corn Syrup (Box 17)
        - H.L. Blaun, Split Flap Carton (Box 17)
        - J.W. Bowman, Apparatus for Handling Chewing Gum (Box 17)
        - G.B. Bradshaw, Process of Making Chicle Substitute (Box 17)
        - W.H. Bradshaw, Refining Process for Certain Raw Gums (Box 17)
        - Wm. H. Bradshaw, Purified Gum (Box 17)
        - B.H. Bramble & E.F. Curry (Box 17)
        - R. Brinkema, Display Case (Box 17)
        - Brinkema, Display Stand (Box 17)
        - Louis H. Britton (Box 17)
        - Brown Bag Filling Machine Company (Box 17)
        - H.J. Brown (Box 17)
        - Orlando J. Buck (Box 17)
        - L.W. Buckley Method of Making Synthetic Chicle (Box 17)
        - L.W. Buckley Synthetic Chicle Compound and Method of Making Same (Box 17)
        - Ludwig Buckley, Synthetic Chicle Compound (Box 17)
        - John Van Buren, Labeling Machine (Box 17)
        - John Van Buren, Packaging Machines (Box 17)
        - J.S. Campbell, Tearing Strips on Packages (Box 17)
        - Franklin Canning (Box 17)
        - F.V. Canning, Golf Ball (Box 17)
        - Jno. H. Carr, Vending Machine (Box 17)
        - Cash Register Display, Improved Design (Box 17)
        - Cellophane Package Wrap, Improvement to Facilitate Opening (Box 17)
        - Cellophane Tablet Package (Box 17)
        - Cellophane Wrapping for Standard Five Stick Brands (Box 17)
        - Charcoal in Gum and Coating (Box 17)
        - Chicle Substitutes and Bases (Box 17)
        - Clark Brothers Chewing Gum Company (Box 17)
        - Maurice C. Clark (Box 17)
        - W.P. Cohoe
          - Antiseptic Chewing Gum (Box 17)
          - Chewing Gum Base (Box 18)
          - Chewing Gum Base and Method (Box 18)
          - Prophylactic Chewing Gum (Box 18)
        - Columbus Vending Machine (Box 18)
        - Consolidated Display Case (Box 18)
        - Consolidated Display Case, Improved Design (Box 18)
        - Philip Corsello, Chewing Gum Wrapper (Box 18)
        - H.W. Cox and D.H. Moore (Box 18)
        - Stuart W. Cramer (Box 18)
        - A.B. Craven (Box 18)
        - E.F. Curry (Box 18)
        - James D. Darling
          - [General], 3 folders (Box 18)
          - Manufacture of Chewing Gum, 2 folders (Box 18)
        - Dating Device, Ball Point Type Ink Applicator (Box 18)
        - Davis and Channing, Method of Purifying Chicle (Box 18)
        - Davis/Channing, Process for Purifying Chicle, Gum or Other Adhesive (Box 18)
        - C.E. Dellenbarger, Breaking-Feeding Device; Rendering Rubber Tasteless and Suitable For Use in Chewing Gum (Box 18)
        - Dentagum Ingredients (Box 18)
        - Dental Medicinal Gum (Box 18)
        - Design for a Display Rack Display Case Patents (Box 18)
        - Jesse Ditson, 2 folders (Box 18)
        - H.V. Dunham, Chewing Gum Base (Box 18)
        - Henry V. Dunham Manufacture of Chewing Gum; Treatment of India Rubber (Box 18)
        - Richard P. Dyckman, Milling of Rubber for Chewing Gum Base (Box 18)
        - Ekert, Chewing Gum (Box 18)
        - Ekert, Drying and/or Coating Apparatus (Box 18)
        - Ekert's Screen Tumbling Device (Box 18)
        - Elbel Patent Use of Tergitol 4-T in Dentifrices (Box 18)
        - Carleton Ellis
          - Chewing Gum Product (Box 18)
          - Composition Containing a Resinous Complex (Box 18)
          - Hydrogenated Oil Composition (Box 18)
          - Oxidized Resinous Product (Box 18)
          - Plastic Reaction Products of PhenOlic Compounds with SulfUr Halides (Box 18)
        - Enzymes in Gum (Box 18)
        - Everett, Display Case (Box 18)
        - Alfred Falk, Manufacture of Chewing Gum (Box 18)
        - FASCAP, Closure of Collapsible Tubes (Box 18)
        - Fink, Display Rack (Box 18)
        - Foil Mounted, Wrapping Materials (Box 18)
        - Foil Sealed Package Tab (Box 18)
        - F.A. Garbutt
          - Chewing Gum Mixing Method (Box 18)
          - Method of Forming Chewing Gum (Box 18)
          - Chewing Gum Machine (Box 18)
        - Geller
          - Chewing Gum Bases, 2 folders (Box 18)
          - Chicle Substitute (Box 18)
        - Gems Tab Package (Box 18)
        - General, 1919-1947; 24 folders (Box 18)
        - General, 1948-1958; 16 folders (Box 19)
        - Gordon, Processes for the Recovery of Chicle and Similar Gum from Filter Press Residue (Box 19)
        - Gordon Casein Glue (Box 19)
        - Gordon Process for Recovering Chicle from Filter Press Residue (Box 19)
        - Walter R. Groshong, New Style Package for Chewing Gum, 2 folders (Box 19)
        - Gruskin, 2 folders (Box 19)
        - W.J. Hale, Chlorophyll in Chewing Gum (Box 19)
        - Halogens in Chewing Gum (Box 19)
        - M.L. Hamlin, Jelutong Product (Box 19)
        - Geo. J. Hanson, (Chewing Gum) Chix (Box 19)
        - Harrison, Nulapain Formula (Box 19)
        - Hartwig/Lougovoy (Box 19)
        - G.A. Hatherill
          - Chewing Gum Base (Box 19)
          - Method of Making a Chewing Gum Base (Box 19)
          - Process of Producing Resinous Material (Box 19)
        - Eduard Heber, A Process of Obtaining Gum from Vegetable Matter (Box 19)
        - R. Heggie, Co-Polymers of Polyvinyl Acetate (Box 19)
        - Robert Heggie, Permanently Flavored Chewing Gum Base (Box 19)
        - Hein and Shafer, Chlorophyll and Urea in Combination to Retard Dental Caries (Box 19)
        - Emil Heinrich, Cutting Mechanism (Box 19)
        - T.E. Heppenstall, Process and Apparatus for Determining Moisture Content (Box 19)
        - Eric J. Hewitt, Chewing Gum Base Material (Box 20)
        - Hewitt, Maleic Anhydride Adducts of Talloel (Box 20)
        - Hewitt, Polyester and Polyamide Resins (Box 20)
        - Hoopes, Coating Apparatus Adapted for Confections (Box 20)
        - Penrose R. Hoops, Coating Machine (Box 20)
        - Hoops Continuous Coating Machine (Box 20)
        - Hopper Box Trunks (Box 20)
        - Messrs. Howe, Pickett and Dean (Box 20)
        - Tom Huston, 2 folders (Box 20)
        - Hydrogenated Oils in Gum (Box 20)
        - Improvement in Boxes (Box 20)
        - Incorporation of Syrup in Gum (Box 20)
        - Inspection Machine for Candy Coated Chewing Gum (Box 20)
        - "Iodigum" (Box 20)
        - Dean M. Jackman, Chicle Substitute (Box 20)
        - Jackman, Chicle Substitutes (Box 20)
        - Jumbo Plug Disc Feature (Box 20)
        - Frank Y. Keator (Box 20)
        - G.F. Kelly Display Box (Box 20)
        - Gerald F. Kelly (Box 20)
        - Weston W. Kilbourn (Box 20)
        - King and Adsit (Box 20)
        - Guy King (Box 20)
        - A. Kneaskern (Box 20)
        - William A. Koneman (Box 20)
        - Labeling Requirements for Iodigum (Box 20)
        - Laminated Candy-Gum Combination (Box 20)
        - L.P. Larson (Box 20)
        - L.P. Larson, Jr. (Box 20)
        - Benj. A. Laws (Box 20)
        - Lewin, Rolaids (Box 20)
        - Lougovoy and Hartwig (Box 20)
        - B.N. Lougovoy, Chewing Gum Base, Zein (Box 20)
        - B.N. Lougovoy, Chewing Gum Base, Thiokel) (Box 20)
        - Thomas J. Lynch (Box 20)
        - Lysozyme and Sugar (Box 20)
        - M. and E. Chicle Melting Kettle (Box 20)
        - Douglas McBean (Box 20)
        - Chas. McDowell (Box 20)
        - John McGavac and George Binnore (Box 20)
        - G.J. Manson (Box 20)
        - H.W. Matheson (Box 20)
        - Medicinal Gums (Box 20)
        - A.G. Meier, 2 folders (Box 20)
        - Kurt Meisenburg (Box 20)
        - Metal Rims for Filter Press Screens (Box 20)
        - Meyer Tin Box (Box 20)
        - Milk of Magnesia Gum (Box 20)
        - Wallace W. Miller (Box 20)
        - Milo Starch (Box 20)
        - Chas. C. Moore (Box 20)
        - Wm. H. Moss (Box 20)
        - Mounting Foil on Cellophane (Box 20)
        - H.M. Mowrey (Box 20)
        - G.B. Mustin (Box 20)
        - Neville Company (Box 20)
        - New and Improved Elastomer (Box 21)
        - New Subway Vending Machine (Box 21)
        - Novelty Ideas for Chewing Gum (Box 21)
        - Emil E. Novotny (Box 21)
        - Nozzle for Dust Elimination (Box 21)
        - Nux Vomica Gum (Box 21)
        - C.F. Obermaier (Box 21)
        - W.W. Odell (Box 21)
        - O'Neill and Simeone (Box 21)
        - O'Neill Ball Machine (Box 21)
        - O'Neill/Simeone (Box 21)
        - P.M. O'Neill, Use of Photo Electric Cell (Box 21)
        - Iwan Ostromislensky (Box 21)
        - Eugene Panza (Box 21)
        - Richard Pasternack (Box 21)
        - Karl E. Peiler (Box 21)
        - Peppermint Flavor Deterioration in Sealed Packages (Box 21)
        - Pepsodent Company (Box 21)
        - Perforated Ball Gum Box (Box 21)
        - Permanently Flexible Gum (Box 21)
        - Peterson, DeLong (Box 21)
        - C.E. Peterson (Box 21)
        - Pickel and Berdick (Box 21)
        - Jos. J. Pilger (Box 21)
        - G.W. Pond (Box 21)
        - Wm. Beach Pratt, Patent no's 1,349,912; 1,349,913; 1,349,914; 1,621,468; 1,240,875; 1,382,669; 1,409,570; 1,240,875; 1,461,675; 1,349,909; 1,380,414; 1,349,911; 1,451,711; 1,349,910; 992,590; 15 folders (Box 21)
        - Printing on Cellophane, I. Curwick (Box 21)
        - Printing on Cellophane, Driver Patent (Box 21)
        - Lysle E. Pritchard (Box 21)
        - Process for Recovery of Gum Constituents from Asclepiadaceae (Box 21)
        - Proposal of Polyelectrolytes Capable of Binding Copper (Box 21)
        - J.D. Pryor (Box 21)
        - Pungs, Wilhelm (Box 21)
        - Earl B. Putt (Box 21)
        - A.P. Rapp (Box 21)
        - Adolph P. Rapp (Box 21)
        - Maria M. Raub (Box 21)
        - P.H. Raymer (Box 21)
        - P.H. Raymer, Incorporation of Milk of Magnesia in Gum (Box 21)
        - Redington and Milmoe, 2 folders (Box 21)
        - Redington Tutti Frutti Machine (Box 21)
        - William A. Reid (Box 21)
        - J. Robinson, Split Flap Carton (Box 21)
        - E.A. Rodman (Box 21)
        - Rose Flavor for Sweet Scent (Box 21)
        - Royalty-Free License Agreement (Box 21)
        - Thos. Sault (Box 21)
        - Sawer and Purves (Box 21)
        - Scanlon and Harrison (Box 21)
        - James J. Scanlon, 3 folders (Box 21)
        - G.P. Schmidt (Box 21)
        - Godfrey P. Schmidt (Box 21)
        - M.C. Schrank (Box 22)
        - Scott and Prouty (Box 22)
        - Scrap Unwrapping Machine (Box 22)
        - Screens in Coating Pans to Prevent Sugar Forming (Box 22)
        - Sears, No Copy (Box 22)
        - Fredlk. Henry Sears (Box 22)
        - Semi Automatic Feeding Device (Box 22)
        - William F. Semple (Box 22)
        - Sen Sen Confection (Box 22)
        - Chas. A. Shattuck (Box 22)
        - Shiek and Cole (Box 22)
        - Shirk, Dental Medicinal Unit (Box 22)
        - Frank Sibley et al. (Box 22)
        - Simeone (Box 22)
        - M.J. Simeone, Date Stamping Device (Box 22)
        - M.J. Simeone, Folding and Gluing Machine (Box 22)
        - Simeone Package for Scotty Gum (Box 22)
        - R. Snedden (Box 22)
        - Richard Snedden (Box 22)
        - Walter Snelling, patent no's 1,288,723; 1,430,034; 1,430,036; 1,315,246; 1,479,330; 6 folders (Box 22)
        - Edgar W. Snyder, patent no. 1,239,313 (Box 22)
        - Wm. A. Steinemann (Box 22)
        - Leon W. Stetson (Box 22)
        - Clarence M. Stiner (Box 22)
        - Stranders Display Rack (Box 22)
        - E.R. Stucky, Glass Display Jar (Box 22)
        - Nathan Sulzberger (Box 22)
        - Sweets Laboratories (Box 22)
        - Synthetic Chewing Gum (Box 22)
        - Synthetic Chicle Substitute (Box 22)
        - Tabletting Research, Silicones (Box 22)
        - Tempters Cellophane Box (Box 22)
        - Tempters Step Display Box (Box 22)
        - Thompson (Box 22)
        - Tibbals Secret Process (Box 22)
        - Tobacco Gum (Box 22)
        - Joseph M. Trimble (Box 22)
        - Amos H. Tyler (Box 22)
        - Use of Maizite (Box 22)
        - Van Buren, Labeling Machs. (Box 22)
        - Vitamins in Chewing Gum (Box 22)
        - Joseph F. Volker (Box 22)
        - Von Foregger (Box 22)
        - Parke H. Watkins (Box 22)
        - Weber, Chewing Gum Base (Box 22)
        - Harry M. Weber, patent no's 1,248,961; 1,402,817; 1,401,452; 3 folders (Box 22)
        - G.R. Webber Weston Cafeteria Rail (Box 22)
        - W.J. White, 2 folders (Box 22)
        - Ira Williams, 1,875,903; 1,908,093, 2 folders (Box 22)
        - Wm. Williams (Box 22)
        - Williams Vending Machine (Box 22)
        - Windown Box and Sectional Opening Flap (Box 22)
        - Van L. Woodward Wrapping Fold (Box 22)
        - Wm. Wrigley Jr. Co. (Box 22)
        - Wrigley P.K. Package (Box 22)
        - Phillip K. Wrigley (Box 22)
        - S.S. Yates (Box 22)
        - Chas. O. Young (Box 22)
        - Yu Chu Vending Machine (Box 22)
    - The Proprietary Association (Box 22)
    - Real Estate
      - Canada, New Factory Building (Box 22)
      - Long Island City (Box 22)
      - Rockford Factory (Box 22)
      - Valley Stream, Long Island (Box 22)
    - Salesman's Jobbing Report, by state
      - A-M (Box 22)
      - M-W (Box 23)
    - Stock
      - Schedule for Annual Meeting of Stockholders (Box 23)
      - Capital Increase, 1956 (Box 24)
      - Capital Stock, Listing on New York Stock Exchange (Box 24)
      - Certification of Increase of Capital Stock and Amendment of Ctf. of Incorporation, 1956 (Box 24)
      - Common Stock, Closed Accounts, 1927-1930; 8 folders (Box 24)
      - Common Stock, Closed Accounts, 1930-1935; 7 folders (Box 25)
      - Common Stock, Closed Accounts, 1934-1935 (Box 26)
      - Dividends
        - General (Box 26)
        - Personal Letter to Stockholders (Box 26)
      - Lost Stock Certificates (Box 26)
      - New York Stock Exchange (Box 26)
      - Preferred Stock, Closed Accounts, 1928 (Box 26)
      - Procedure, Annual Meeting (Box 26)
      - Proxies, 1934-1962; destroyed, Jan 1992 (Box 26-35)
      - Reports, 1916-1931; 48 folders (Box 36)
      - Reports, 1932-1938; 29 folders, 2 volumes (Box 37)
      - Reports, 1939-1955; 57 folders (Box 38)
      - Reports, 1956-1961; 23 folders (Box 39)
      - Reports, 1962; 6 folders (Box 40)
      - Stockholders, 37 folders (Box 40)
      - Voting Trust, Invoices (Box 40)
      - Tax, California Sales and Use, 1956-1958; 2 folders (Box 40)
    - Trade Marks
      - [General] (Box 41)
      - States, A-L (Box 41)
      - States, L-V (Box 42)
      - States, V-W (Box 43)
    - United States Trade Mark Association, 1957 (Box 43)
    - Uruguay, 1956; 1959; 2 folders (Box 43)
  - American Grocery Specialty
    - [General], 1927-1929; 2 folders (Box 43)
  - Banks
    - Bank of Manhattan Trust Company (Box 43)
    - Bankers Trust Company, 1918-1956; 5 folders (Box 43)
    - Chase Manhattan Bank (Box 43)
    - Chase National Bank, 1931-1952 (Box 43)
    - Chemical Bank and Trust Company, 1931-1942 (Box 43)
    - Chemical Corn Exchange Bank, 1956-1957 (Box 43)
  - Albert L. Calder Company
    - [General], 1942-1953 (Box 43)
    - Liquidation (Box 43)
  - Caleb Crawford Company
    - Annual Meeting (Box 43)
    - Crawford Cough Gum (Box 43)
    - Dentagum Circulars (Box 43)
    - Iodigum Circulars (Box 43)
  - Canadian Chewing Gum Company
    - Officers, Directors, Stockholders (Box 43)
    - Copies of Minutes of Directors' Meetings, 1920-1922 (Box 43)
    - Meeting of Board of Directors, 1921 (Box 43)
    - Annual Meeting, 1922 (Box 43)
    - Directors' Meeting, 1922 (Box 43)
    - Meeting of Board of Directors, 1922 (Box 43)
    - Directors' Meeting, 1923 (Box 43)
    - Annual Meeting, 1923 (Box 43)
    - Annual Meeting, 1924 (Box 43)
    - Annual Meeting, 1925 (Box 43)
    - Annual Meeting, 1926 (Box 43)
    - Board of Directors' Meeting, 1926 (Box 43)
    - Annual Meeting, 1927 (Box 43)
    - Annual Meeting, 1928 (Box 43)
    - Board of Directors' Meeting, 1928 (Box 43)
    - Board of Directors' Meeting, 1929 (Box 43)
    - Board of Directors' Meeting, 1930 (Box 43)
    - Annual Meeting, 1932 (Box 43)
    - By-Laws, 1932-1945 (Box 43)
    - Annual Meeting, 1933 (Box 43)
    - Dividend, 1939-1941; 2 folders (Box 43)
  - Canadian Chewing Gum Co., Limited
    - Annual Meeting, 1934; 1935,; 1936; 3 folders (Box 44)
  - Canadian Chewing Gum Sales, Ltd.
    - By-Laws, 1932-1941; 5 folders (Box 44)
  - Chicle Development Company
    - New York City, 1922 (Box 44)
    - By-Laws, 1941-1947 (Box 44)
    - Correspondence, 1945-1950 (Box 44)
    - Annual Meeting, 1949-1953 (Box 44)
    - Correspondence, 1951-1955 (Box 44)
    - Annual Meeting, 1955-1957 (Box 44)
  - Corporation Trust Company
    - [General], 1926-1952 (Box 44)
  - Crawford Gum Company
    - Liquidation (Box 44)
    - [General], 1950-1955 (Box 44)
  - Fiduciary Trust Company of New York
    - [General], 1931-1950 (Box 44)
  - First National Bank of Chicago
    - [General], 1923 (Box 44)
  - Registrar and Transfer Company
    - Receipts (Box 44)
    - Invoices, 1941-1956 (Box 44)
    - Correspondence, 1947-1954 (Box 44)
  - Sen-Sen Chiclet Company
    - Minute Book, Directors and Exec. Com. Meetings (Box 44)
    - Minute Book, Stockholders Meetings (Box 44)
- Financial papers
  The following are all bound volumes.
  - Adams and Son
    - Cash Book, 1889-1894
    - Cash Book, 1902-1909
    - Journal, General Cash, 1890-1903
    - Journal Private, 1904-1906
    - Journal Preferred Stock Dividend, 1891-1899
    - Journal Preferred Stock Dividend, 1891-1892
    - Dividend Ledger, 1900-1904
  - Adams Chewing Gum Company
    - General Ledger, 1932
  - American Chicle Company
    - Advances to Salesmen and Others, 1952-1963; 11 volumes
    - Advances to Salesmen and Others, Auto Dept., 1948-1953
    - Advertising Stock, 1945-1955
    - Analysis of Cash Journal, 1906-1913
    - Analysis, Salesmen, 1963-1964
    - Appraisals, A.C. Company, 1916; 1922; 11 volumes
    - Bill List, Houston, San Francisco, Chicago, 1951-1954
    - Cafeteria, Current, 1960-1961
    - Cafeteria, Cash Receipts and Disbursements, 1957-1963
    - Cafeteria, Invoice Register, 1949-1955
    - Cafeteria, Journal and Ledger, 1946-1954
    - Cafeteria, Operating Statement, 1932-1959; 5 volumes
    - Cash Books, 1960-1962; 4 volumes
    - Cash Books, General, 1902-1914; 4 volumes
    - Cash Book, Chicago and San Francisco, 1951-1953
    - Cash Book, Houston, 1956
    - Cash Collections, 1949-1950
    - Cash Disbursements, General, 1922-1955; 6 volumes
    - Cash Disbursements, Uruguay, 1951-1954
    - Cash Receipts, General, 1942-1959; 9 volumes
    - Cash Receipts and Disbursements, 1930-1932
    - Cash Receipts and Disbursements, Chicago, 1936-1953; 6 volumes
    - Cash Receipts and Disbursements, San Francisco, 1926-1929; 1936-1959; 7 volumes
    - Cash Receipts and Disbursements, Houston, 1938-1941; 1946-1950; 2 volumes
    - Compensation Binder, Coleman, San Francisco, 1930-1939
    - Daily Financial Statements, Canada, Houston, San Francisco, 1951-1954
    - Essential Oils Stored in Public Warehouses, 1962
    - Expenses Prepaid and Accrued, 1949-1957; 4 volumes
    - Expenses, Salesmen, 1955
    - Expenses, Long Island City, 1959-1960; 2 volumes
    - Finished Goods, Inventories, 1952-1960; 2 volumes
    - Finished Goods, Inventories, Houston, 1945-1948
    - Finished Goods, Inventories, L.I.C., 1931-1946; 1940-1941,; 1961; 3 volumes
    - Finished Goods, Inventories, Warehouses, 1950-1953; 1954; 2 volumes
    - Flavors and Ingredients, 1947-1954; 1960-1963; 2 volumes
    - Insurance Ledgers, 1937-1952; 2 volumes
    - Inventories, Cost Dept., 1933-1951
    - Inventories, Wholesale Charges, 1946-1950
    - Inventories, San Francisco and Chicago, 1926
    - Inventories, San Francisco, Chicago, Canada, 1931
    - Inventories, San Francisco, Chicago, Houston, 1950-1959; 2 volumes
    - Invoice Registers, 1916-1962; 47 volumes
    - Invoice Register, Rockford, 1956-1957
    - Journal, 1904-1905
    - Journal, Accounts Receivable, 1940; 1944-1948,; 1958-1961; 3 volumes
    - Journal, Cash, 1916-1917
    - Journal, Cost, 1899-1907; 1910-1911,; 1932-1951,; 1956-1961; 8 volumes
    - Journal, Dividend, 1907-1909
    - Journal, Factory, 1914-1916
    - Journals, General, 1954-1959; 3 volumes
    - Journal, General, Authorization for Entries, 1925-1949; 1950-1954; 13 volumes
    - Journal, General, Venezuela, 1945-1952; 3 volumes
    - Journal, General, Mexico, 1944
    - Journals, General, 1912-1914; 1916,; 1922-1924,; 1931-1934; 8 volumes
    - Journal, Private Dividend, 1903-1905
    - Journal, Purchase, 1916-1917
    - Journals, Sales, 1917; 1920,; 1925-1927,; 1932,; 1934,; 1936-1937,; 1940,; 1946-1947,; 1949-1950,; 1958-1960; 10 volumes
    - Ledger Box and Carton Materials, 1954-1959; 1961-1962; 2 volumes
    - Ledgers, Cost, San Francisco, 1924-1942; 3 volumes
    - Ledger, Cost, San Francisco, Chicago, 1931-1934
    - Ledgers, Cost, 1942-1945; 1957-1960; 4 volumes
    - Ledger, Cost, L.I.C., 1946-1953; 1956-1957; 4 volumes
    - Ledger, Cost, Venezuela, 1942-1951; 2 volumes
    - Ledger, General, 1916-1918
    - Ledger, Cost Dept., Chicle, 1937-1942
    - Ledgers, General, 1918-1958; 16 volumes
    - Ledgers, Transfer, 1919-1925; 1919-1937,; 1920-1950; 3 volumes
    - Ledger, Journal, 1906-1909
    - Ledger, Prepaid and Accruals, 1945-1948
    - Ledger, Warehouse Data Distribution, 1942-1945
    - Ledger, Materials Stored in Public Warehouses, 1959-1962
    - Ledger, Materials, Factory Expense, 1950-1959
    - Ledger, Materials and Supplies, Mints, 1953; 1959-1963; 2 volumes
    - Ledger, Materials and Supplies, Raw Materials, 1960-1963
    - Ledger, Materials and Supplies, Wrapping Materials, 1958-1963; 2 volumes
    - Patents, 1909
    - Premiums, 1935-1942
    - Research and Development, Materials, Includes, 1961-1963
    - Shipping Expense, 1962-1964
    - Shipping Materials, 1959-1962